让我们用现实世界的图像将其中的一部分付诸实践。
Let’s put some of this into practice with a real world image.
我将在实验室中加载一个包含一些西红柿的场景图像，
I am going to load an image of a scene that comprises some tomatoes on a bush in a lab,
我将转换图像，以便像素在MATLAB中存储为double
and I am going to convert the image so that the pixels are stored inside MATLAB as double
精确数字。
precision numbers.
所以我们可以看一下广告中的图像：它里面有一些西红柿
So we can have a look at the image as advertised: it contains some tomatoes on a bush inside
实验室-实际上在麻省理工学院。
a lab — at MIT, actually.
如果我点击图像，我们可以看到番茄中的像素已经相当
If I click around on the image we can see that the pixels in the tomato have got quite
大量的红色，65％的红色，绿色不多，蓝色不多。
a large amount of red, 65 per cent red, not much green, not much blue.
现在，叶子，例如茎，含有比红色或蓝色更多的绿色。
Now the leaves, the stems for instance, contain more green than they do red or blue.
番茄图像很有趣;西红柿实际上非常有光泽，如果我点击一下
The tomato images are interesting; the tomatoes are actually quite shiny and if I click around
在这里，我们看到该值实际上更接近白色而不是红色。
here we see that the value is actually closer to white than it is to red.
这个区域在这里我们称之为镜面高光。
This region here we refer to as a specular highlight.
发生的事情是房间内的明亮光线从表面反射出来
What has happened is that bright light within the room is reflecting off the surface of
西红柿是一种镜面而不是淡化的方式，在这种情况下，光没有
the tomato in a specular rather than a defuse fashion and in this case the light has not
拿起水果的颜色，基本上我们在这里看到的是颜色
picked up the color of the fruit, it is basically what we are seeing here is the color of the
光源本身。
light source itself.
我们已经讨论了几次伽玛编码信息的过程
We have talked a couple of times already about the process of gamma encoding the information
在文件中的图像内。
within an image in a file.
但我想要做的是取消伽玛编码;我想应用伽玛
But what I would like to do is to undo that gamma encoding; I would like to apply a gamma
校正或伽玛解码，我可以通过传入iread功能
correction or gamma decoding and I can do that with the iread function by passing in
一个额外的参数，并传递我想要应用的伽玛值
an extra argument and passing in the gamma value that I would like to have applied to
每个像素。
every pixel.
因此，这将消除相机观察到的亮度之间的非线性
So this will eliminate the non-linearity between the luminance that the camera observed and
我在MATLAB工作区中的像素值。
the pixel values that I have in my MATLAB workspace.
如果我显示这个经过伽马校正的图像，我们会发现它看起来很不寻常
If I display this gamma corrected image we will see that it looks rather unusual, it
看起来实际上非常黑暗，正如之前所解释的那样，这里发生了什么
looks actually quite dark and as explained before what has happened here is that the
伽马校正现已应用两次。
gamma correction has now been applied twice.
我已经在软件和我正在查看图像的显示器上应用了一次
I have applied it once in software and the monitor that I am looking at the image on
也正在应用伽马校正。
is also applying the gamma correction.
因此，我工作区中的值现在是线性的，这看起来并不正确
So it doesn’t look right that the values that I have in my workspace are now linearly
与进入镜头镜头的光有关。
related to the light that went into the lens of the camera.
所以接下来我要做的就是显示一个颜色平面
So the next thing that I would like to do is just to display one of the color planes
在这张图片中。
in this image.
所以让我们显示红色的飞机，它就在这里，我们可以看到番茄
So let’s display the red plane and here it is here, and we can see that the tomato
水果在这里看起来很明亮，因为它们反射了大量的红光，而在
fruits are looking quite bright here because they reflect a lot of red light, whereas in
绿色的飞机，我们看到水果看起来非常，非常，黑暗。
the green plane we see that the fruit looks very, very, dark.
我们将颜色值分开。
Let’s separate out the color values.
我将创建一个名为R的新工作区变量，其中包含每行中的像素
I am going to create a new workspace variable called R which contains pixels in every row
以及属于第一个平面的每一列。
and every column that belong to plane one.
我将为绿色飞机做类似的事情，我将做类似的事情
I am going to do a similar thing for the green plane and I am going to do a similar thing
对于蓝色平面，即3号平面。
for the blue plane, which is plane number 3.
所以，例如，我可以再次显示我刚刚计算的绿色平面。
So, for instance, I can just display again the green plane that I just computed.
现在我要做的下一件事是计算色度坐标和
Now the next thing that I want to do is to compute the chromaticity coordinates and to
这样做我需要计算红色和绿色和蓝色的总和，我要去
do that I need to compute the sum of the red and the green and the blue and I am going
把它放入名为Y的局部变量中。
to put that into the local variable called Y.
Y是用于所谓亮度图像的常用符号;这是一张单色图片
Y is a common symbol used for what is called the luminance image; it’s a monochrome image
其实。
actually.
如果我们现在看一下它会看起来像单色或黑白图片
If we look at this now it will look something like a monochrome or black and white picture
现场。
of the scene.
它是所有颜色通道的平均值。
It is the average of all of the color channels.
现在，色度坐标计算出所有像素之间的比率
Now the chromaticity coordinates computes the ratio between all of the pixels in the
红色平面和总和，我可以使用MATLAB计算这个元素明智的划分
red plane and the sum and I can compute this element wise division by using the MATLAB
运算符点斜杠，所以它要做的是计算一个新的图像，调用它
operator dot slash, so what it is going to do is to compute a new image, call it little
R，其尺寸与资本R和资本Y的尺寸相同。
R, and its dimensions will be the same as the dimensions of capital R and capital Y.
图像中的每个元素littleR是大写R中的对应像素除以
Each element of the image little R is the corresponding pixel in capital R divided by
大写字母Y中的相应像素。
the corresponding pixel in capital Y.
让我为绿色色度通道做同样的事情;我们来看一下
And let me do the same thing for the green chromaticity channel; let’s have a look
在这些。
at these.
这些存储在MATLAB工作空间矩阵中，但我当然可以显示矩阵
These are stored in the MATLAB workspaces matrices, but of course I can display a matrix
作为图像和图像被表示为矩阵，所以这里是小R，我可以创建
as an image and an image is represented as a matrix, so here is little R and I can create
另一个图，图二，在图二中，我将显示小G.
another figure, figure two, and in figure two I am going to display little G.
所以这些是色度值，如果我们在这里探讨一些值
So these are the chromaticity values, and if we poke around some of the values here
我们可以看到水果在哪里，它有很大的R值，它有一个非常的
we can see that where the fruit is, it has got quite a large value of R, it has a very
小G.的小值
small value of little G.
如果我们看一下叶子的哪个位置，我们就会看到它们具有适度的值
If we look at where some of the leaves are we see that they have got a modest value of
小R-约0.39-和小G有一个稍大的值，所以这两个图像
little R—about 0.39—and little G has got a slightly bigger value, so these two images
代表这个场景中的颜色：我们已经考虑了强度。
represent the color in this scene: we have factored out the intensity.
现在让我们说我们想制定一个可以选择属于的像素的规则
So let’s say now that we wanted to make a rule that would select a pixel that belonged
对水果而言并不属于任何其他事物。
to the fruit and didn’t belong to anything else.
很明显，我们想要一条规则来说明R似乎很大的事实
Well clearly we want a rule that said something about the fact that R is quite big, it seems
至少大于0.8，大多数是0.9以上，但保守地说，
to be at least greater than 0.8 and mostly it is above 0.9, but let’s say, conservatively,
它必须高于0.8，在这种情况下，我们希望G值必须非常小。
it has to be above 0.8 and in this case we want the G value has to be quite small.
你应该知道，甚至不到0.1。
Has to be sort of, you know, less than 0.1 even.
但保守一点，我们说它必须小于0.2。
But to be conservative, let’s say it has to be less than 0.2.
所以我可以创建一个新变量，它将成为一个逻辑变量，所以我要去
So I could create a new variable, it is going to be a logical variable, so I am going to
如果R大于0.8且G小于0.2，那么它就是真的。
say anywhere that R is greater than 0.8 and G is less than 0.2 it will be true.
所以让我们显示我刚刚创建的名为Tom的图像，我们就拥有了它。
So let’s display this image I just created called Tom and there we have it.
这里的背景，这些值都是零，它们都是假的，在这里它们
The background here, these values are all zero, they are all false and in here they
都具有一个值，这是MATLAB表示真实概念的方式。
all have values of one, which is MATLAB’s way of representing the concept of true.
我们现在创建了一个二进制图像，如果它们是番茄果实，则像素为1
We have created now a binary image where the pixels are one if they are the tomato fruit
如果它不是水果，背景，人和叶子，它们就是零。
and they are zero if it is not the fruit, background, people and leaves.
现在我们有了二进制图像，我们可以做很多我们之前演示过的事情
Now that we have a binary image we can do a lot of the things that we demonstrated earlier
当我们谈论二元视觉时。
when we were talking about binary vision.
所以我可以找到这个图像中的所有blob，所以我应用了iblobs
So I could look for all of the blobs that are within this image so I apply the iblobs
功能到我们刚刚计算的二进制图像，在这里，它有十个blob
function to the binary image we just computed and here it is, that there are ten blobs in
这里。
here.
现在，显然有几个大斑点，我们可以看到那里，有一些斑点
Now, there are clearly a couple of big blobs and we can see there, there are some blobs
面积相当大，周围也有很多非常非常小的斑点
with quite a large area and there is also a lot of very, very small blobs around the
其中一个水果的边缘。
edge of one of the fruit.
现在我们可以回到原始图像，让我们看看图一和那里
Now we can go back to the original image, let’s have a look at figure one and there
我将显示原始图像，然后我将覆盖一些边界框
I am going to display the original image and then I am going to overlay some bounding boxes
然后我将它们覆盖在绿色中。
and I will overlay them in the color green.
因此，我们有它;很简单，我们拍摄了彩色图像，我们已经计算了
So there we have it; quite simply, we have taken a color image, we have computed the
在色度坐标方面，每个像素的基本颜色。
essential color at each of the pixels in terms of chromaticity coordinates.
我们制定了一个非常简单的规则来选择属于水果的像素，而不是
We have made a very simple rule to choose pixels that belong to the fruit and not to
还要别的吗;这导致我们得到一个二进制图像。
anything else; that led us to a binary image.
一旦我们有了二进制图像，那么我们就可以应用我们已经拥有的所有技术
Once we have a binary image, then we can apply all of the techniques that we have already
我学会并以非常快速的方式概述了特定的水果。
learnt and in very quick fashion I can outline the particular fruit.
现在问题在于水果是一种畸形，其中一部分是因为
Now the problem with this is that the fruit are kind of misshapen, part of that is because
我之前提到过的镜面反射，以及一些水果都被模糊了
of the specular reflection that I mentioned earlier and also some of the fruit is obscured
通过树叶和其他任何东西，仍然是一个开始的边界框，我们可以看看
by leaves and whatever, still the bounding box is a good place to start, we could look
在我们之前使用的一些数学形态学技术中，我们可以应用这些技术
at some of the mathematical morphology techniques that we used before, we could apply the techniques
膨胀和侵蚀可能填补了这些水果中一些缺失的部分。
of dilation and erosion perhaps to fill in some of the missing part of those fruit.